Mittenthal, Richard Papers 6407
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Oakland Press through Owens-Illinois, 1961-2002 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 19: Owens - Illinois, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 9)
    11/17/1975
- PBM Industries through Pentwater Wire, 1963-2005 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: PBM Indiana, 1993; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 10)
    9/26/1993
  - Item 2: Packaging Corporation of America, 1993; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 10)
    9/20/1993
  - Item 3: Packaging Corporation of America, 1994; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: City of Palm Coast, Florida, 2005; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 10)
    6/14/2005
  - Item 5: Parker Davis & Company, 1963; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 10)
    1/30/1963
  - Item 6: Parker Hanifin Company, 2001; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 10)
    1/10/2001
  - Item 7: Peerless Cement Company, 1963; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 10)
    12/4/1963
  - Item 8: Peerless Cement Company, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 10)
    10/27/1975
  - Item 9: Peerless Cement Company, 1963; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 10)
    3/31/1963
  - Item 10: Process Metals, 1995; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 10)
    10/11/1995
  - Item 11: Pennsalt Chemicals Corporation, 1964; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 10)
    11/4/1964
  - Item 12: Penn Electric, 1988; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 10)
    1/20/1988
  - Item 13: Penn Electric, 1989; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 10)
    5/10/1989
  - Item 14: Penn Power Company, 1968; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 10)
    9/17/1968
  - Item 15: Penn Walt Corporation, 1972; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 10)
    6/10/1972
  - Item 16: Penn Walt Corporation, 1978; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 10)
    2/10/1978
  - Item 17: Penn Walt Corporation, 1981; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 10)
    10/26/1981
  - Item 18: Pentimeter Wine Products, 1993; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 10)
    8/31/1993
- People's Gas Light and Coke through Pontiac Board of Education, 1955-2003 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Peoples Gas Light & Coke Company, 1993; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 11)
    9/30/1993
  - Item 2: Permelastic Products Company, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 11)
    6/15/1976
  - Item 3: Peschke Siausage Company, 1955; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 11)
    2/28/1955
  - Item 4: Petrolium Specialties, 1961; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 11)
    10/27/1961
  - Item 5: Pete Eckrich & Sons, 1993; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: Petro - Lube, 1998; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 11)
    3/1/1998
  - Item 7: Phamacia & Upjohn, 1998; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 11)
    9/30/1998
  - Item 8: Phillips Petrolium Company, 1964; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 11)
    8/11/1964
  - Item 9: Pittsburgh Tube Company, 1991; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 11)
    10/8/1991
  - Item 10: Plain Dealer Publeshay Company, 1982; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Item 11: Plex Company, 1987; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 11)
    3/11/1987
  - Item 12: RL Polk & Company, 1964; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 11)
    5/25/1964
  - Item 13: RL Polk & Company, 1966; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 11)
    2/18/1966
  - Item 14: 50 District Ct (Public Employees), 1998; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 11)
    11/20/1998
  - Item 15: City of Pontiac, 2003; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 11)
    3/28/2003
  - Item 16: City of Pontiac, 2003; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 11)
    6/11/2003
  - Item 17: City of Pontiac, 1988; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 11)
    9/12/1988
  - Item 18: Board of Education Pontiac, 1966; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 11)
    2/24/1966
- Port Authority of Allegheny County through Public Service Company of Indiana, 1961-1999 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Port Authority of Alleghang County, 1982; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 12)
    1/7/1982
  - Item 2: Port Clinton Mfg Company, 1966; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 12)
    2/1/1966
  - Item 3: Potomac Steel Corporation, 1980; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 12)
    12/23/1980
  - Item 4: Power Vacation Services, 1999; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 12)
    2/22/1999
  - Item 5: Precision Hardware, 1961; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 12)
    7/14/1961
  - Item 6: Prestolute - Etha Corporation, 1964; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 12)
    3/15/1964
  - Item 7: Proctor & Gamble Poyser Products, 1983; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 12)
    4/28/1983
  - Item 8: Proctor & Gamble Poyser Products, 1993; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 12)
    3/15/1993
  - Item 9: Proctor & Gamble Poyser Products, 1989; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 12)
    1/23/1989
  - Item 10: Proctor & Gamble Poyser Products, 1996; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 12)
    11/22/1996
  - Item 11: Prudencial Insuance Company, 1991; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 12)
    9/19/1991
  - Item 12: Public Service Company - Co., 1995; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 12)
    2/15/1995
  - Item 13: Public Service Company of Indiana, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 12)
    11/11/1974
- Quality Service/Togo through Regional Transportation District, 1960-2000 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Reality Spring Hogs, 1993; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 13)
    9/28/1993
  - Item 2: RM Titanium Company, 1999; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 13)
    11/3/1999
  - Item 3: Randal NY Company, 1995; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 13)
    4/28/1995
  - Item 4: Rapistan Dematic Corporation, 1998; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 13)
    12/10/1998
  - Item 5: Ravenswood Aluminum Corporation, 1997; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 13)
    5/1/1997
  - Item 6: Regional Transportation District Denver Colorado, 1988; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 13)
    4/7/1988
- Reliance Steel through Rowe International, 1962-2002 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Remington Rand, Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Reserve Mining Company, 1967; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: Reynolds Metal Company, Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: Rheem NY Company, 2002; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 14)
    9/5/2002
  - Item 5: Rock Tenn Company Stage Mill, 1993; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 14)
    12/6/1993
  - Item 6: Rockwell International Corporation, 1997; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 14)
    5/27/1997
  - Item 7: Roseville Community Schools, 1996; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 14)
    2/29/1996
  - Item 8: Rowe International, 1971; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 14)
- S and R Equipment through Simonds Worden White, 1956-2004 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: S v. R Cequptment Co., 2001; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 15)
    6/12/2001
  - Item 2: Saginaw Count Mental Health Association, 2002; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 15)
    3/6/2002
  - Item 3: Saginaw Count Mental Health Association, 2002; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 15)
    3/20/2002
  - Item 4: Saginaw Count Mental Health Association, 2004; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 15)
    4/19/2004
  - Item 5: Board of Education Saginaw Public Schools, 1997; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 15)
    5/16/1997
  - Item 6: Sara Lee Bakery, 2003; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 15)
    8/6/2003
  - Item 7: Saylor - Beall Mf. Company, 1983; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 15)
    1/25/1983
  - Item 8: R.P. Sderer Corp, 1959; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 15)
    10/1/1959
  - Item 9: H. Scocroft Company, 1962; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 15)
    6/20/1962
  - Item 10: Sears Robuck, 2002; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Item 11: Seaway Food Town, 1992; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 15)
    6/12/1992
  - Item 12: Semco Energy Gas Company, 1998; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Item 13: Semet - Solvay Corporation, 1963; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 15)
    1/8/1963
  - Item 14: STEP, 1998; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Item 15: Seven-Up Detroit, 1997; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 15)
    9/5/1997
  - Item 16: Shacon Steel Corporation, 1969; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Item 17: Shacon Steel Corporation, 1970; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 15)
    6/1/1970
  - Item 18: Shacon Steel Corporation, 1981; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 15)
    12/15/1981
  - Item 19: Steel Workers & Brotherhood of Carpenters & Joiners, 2005; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 15)
    8/15/2005
  - Item 20: Simerds Worden White Company, 1956; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 15)
    3/30/1956
- Simpson Industries through Southwestern Bell Telephone, 1963-2005 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Simpson Industries, 1993; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 16)
    11/24/1993
  - Item 2: A.O. Smith Corpoation, 1971; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 16)
    2/18/1971
  - Item 3: H.A. Smith Packery Company, 1963; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Item 4: Smurfit-Stone Corporation, 2005; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 16)
    10/3/2005
  - Item 5: Smurfit-Stone Corporation, 2003; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 16)
    1/22/2003
  - Item 6: Socomy Mobel Oil Company, 1964; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 16)
    2/22/1964
  - Item 7: Social Security Administration - Hearings & Appeal, 2002; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 16)
    2/1/2002
  - Item 8: Social Security Administration - Hearings & Appeal, 2002; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 16)
    6/27/2002
  - Item 9: South Bend Lathe, 1982; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 16)
    5/13/1982
  - Item 10: South Bend Public Transportation, 1982; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 16)
    8/19/1982
  - Item 11: Southeastern Michigan Transportation Authority, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 16)
    12/27/1977
  - Item 12: Southern Bell Telephone & Telegraph Company, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 16)
    9/6/1977
  - Item 13: South Lyon Community School Distict, 1978; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 16)
    4/21/1978
  - Item 14: Southwest Ohio Regional Transit, 1989; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 16)
    7/1/1989
  - Item 15: Southwestern Bell Telephone, 2002; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 16)
    5/1/2002
  - Item 16: Southwestern Bell Telephone, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 16)
    2/10/1975
  - Item 17: Southwestern Bell Telephone, 2000; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Specifications Service through Strick Corporation, 1959-2000 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Specifications Services Company, 1999; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 17)
    12/17/1999
  - Item 2: Spery Vickers, 1983; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: Spery Vickers, 1983; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 17)
    3/3/1983
  - Item 4: Springfield Machine & Stamping, 1959; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Item 5: Square D Company, 1982; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 17)
    9/29/1982
  - Item 6: Board of Public Works - St. Clair County, 1992; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 17)
    11/2/1992
  - Item 7: St. Clair Rubber Company, 1980; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 17)
    12/5/1980
  - Item 8: St. Clair Rubber Company, 1962; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 17)
    7/13/1962
  - Item 9: City of St. Clair Shores, 1988; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 17)
    6/17/1988
  - Item 10: St. Clair Aluminum, 2000; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 17)
    2/28/2000
  - Item 11: Standard Forgings Corporation, 1963; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 17)
    10/17/1963
  - Item 12: Standard Oil Company Lima Refinery, 1964; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 17)
    6/13/1964
  - Item 13: Standard Tube Co, 1969; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Item 14: Sterling Vision Shopper, 1990; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 17)
    11/19/1990
  - Item 15: Detroit Restaurant Grill, 1961; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 17)
    6/13/1961
  - Item 16: Detroit Restaurant Grill, 1964; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 17)
    8/24/1964
  - Item 17: Michigan Panelyte Molded Plastics St. Reges Paper, 1962; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 17)
    6/29/1962
  - Item 18: Stuck Coporation, 1968; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 17)
    10/19/1968
- Stroh Brewing through Syntel, 1965-2003 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Stron Brewing Company, 1979; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 18)
    12/7/1979
  - Item 2: Sturgis Newport Business Forum, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 18)
    6/1/1974
  - Item 3: Super Food Service, 1965; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: Super Food Service, 2003; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 18)
    3/27/2003
  - Item 5: Superior Linen Service, 1998; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 18)
    2/3/1998
  - Item 6: Swift & Company, 1978; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 18)
    2/24/1978
  - Item 7: Swift & Company, 1978; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 18)
    6/24/1978
  - Item 8: Swift & Company, 1978; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 18)
    12/25/1978
  - Item 9: Swift & Company, 1979; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 18)
    4/11/1979
  - Item 10: Swift Independent Packing, 1978; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Item 11: Swift Independent Packing, 1978; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 18)
    6/10/1978
  - Item 12: Swift Independent Packing, 1985; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 18)
    5/13/1985
  - Item 13: Syntel, 2000; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 18)
    6/19/2000
- Talbert Manufacturing through Titanium Metals Corporations, 1961-2005 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Thompson Electric Welder Company, 1961; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 19)
    11/7/1961
  - Item 1: Talbert NY Company, 2005; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 19)
    6/9/2005
  - Item 2: City of Taylor, 1995; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 19)
    6/5/1995
  - Item 2: Thorofare Markets, 1983; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 19)
    2/23/1983
  - Item 3: Taylor Forge Division, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 19)
    3/17/1975
  - Item 3: Thunder Bay NY Corporation, 1999; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 19)
    2/5/1999
  - Item 4: Titanium Metals Company of America, 1971; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 19)
    2/1/1971
  - Item 4: Taylor & Gaskin, Incorporated, 1962; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 19)
    11/16/1962
  - Item 5: Titanium Metals Company of America, 1981; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 19)
    8/19/1981
  - Item 5: Taylor School District, 1999; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 19)
    10/25/1999
  - Item 6: Tecumseh Corugated Box, 1999; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 19)
    11/2/1999
  - Item 6: Titanium Metals Company of America, 1981; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 19)
    10/19/1981
  - Item 7: Teledyne Continental Motors, 1988; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 19)
    8/22/1988
  - Item 8: Teledyne Cal, 1996; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 19)
    12/13/1996
  - Item 9: Evait Products Company, 1995; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 19)
    3/6/1995
  - Item 10: Thermo King Corporation, 1997; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 19)
    9/18/1997
  - Item 11: Thomas Steel Sip Corporation, 1988; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 19)
    1/6/1988
  - Item 12: Thompson Chrysler-Plymouth, 1989; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 19)
    9/4/1989
- Tokheim Corporation through Typographical Union No. 18, 1960-2000 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Tokheim Corporation, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 1)
    12/8/1975
  - Item 2: Toledo Blade Company, 1991; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 1)
    7/19/1991
  - Item 3: Toledo Edison Company 3/17/04, 1990; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 1)
    5/22/1990
  - Item 4: Traffic Transport Eng. In, 1960; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 1)
    8/6/1960
  - Item 5: Traffic Transport Eng. In, 1965; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 1)
    6/7/1965
  - Item 6: Tribune Publishing Company, 1989; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Tribune Publishing Company, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 1)
    12/6/1976
  - Item 8: City of Troy (Police), 1991; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 1)
    8/6/1991
  - Item 9: Trinity Industries, 2000; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 1)
    6/12/2000
  - Item 10: City of Troy, Michigan - (Police), 1994; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 1)
    6/20/1994
  - Item 11: Board of Education - Troy School District, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 1)
    5/23/1977
  - Item 12: True Temper Corporation, 1979; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 1)
    8/6/1979
  - Item 13: True Temper Corporation, 1979; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 1)
    7/13/1979
  - Item 14: Trube Turns, 1980; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 1)
    4/14/1980
  - Item 15: Twigg Industries (Pryor NY Company), 1958; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 1)
    7/29/1958
  - Item 16: Twin City Foods, 1996; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 1)
    6/10/1996
  - Item 17: Typographical Arts Association of Michigan, 1961; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 1)
    10/16/1961
- UAW through Univex Die Casting, 1959-2003 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Staff Council of International Representatives - UAW, 2001; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 2)
    7/29/2001
  - Item 1: Univesal Atlas Cement U.S. Steel, 1966; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 2)
    7/25/1966
  - Item 2: Staff Council of International Representatives - UAW, 2001; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 2)
    12/5/2001
  - Item 2: Univesal Atlas Cement U.S. Steel, 1968; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 2)
    2/10/1968
  - Item 3: Office Employees - International Union CEIU - UAW, 1963; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 2)
    12/21/1963
  - Item 3: Univey Die Case & Eng Company, 1964; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 2)
    5/4/1964
  - Item 4: United Daives Incorporated, 1961; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 2)
    12/20/1961
  - Item 5: U.S. Graphite Company - Wickers Corporation, 1961; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 2)
    5/22/1961
  - Item 6: FAIR (Federation of Agends & International Representation), 1996; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 2)
    1/2/1996
  - Item 7: United Parcel Service, 2002; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 2)
    4/11/2002
  - Item 8: United Parcel Service, 2003; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 2)
    4/30/2003
  - Item 9: U.S. Industries - Gage Division, 1972; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 2)
    12/4/1972
  - Item 10: U.S. Manufacturing Company, 1992; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 2)
    3/2/1992
  - Item 11: United Technologies, 1997; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 2)
    10/1/1997
- Valley Mould and Iron through Vulcan Chain, 1964-2003 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Valley Mould & Iron Company, 1970; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 3)
    5/11/1970
  - Item 2: Deparment of Veteran Afffairs - VA Medical Center, 2000; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 3)
    5/16/2000
  - Item 3: Vickers Incorporated, 2015; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 3)
    5/29/2015
  - Item 4: Vickers Incorporated, 1965; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 3)
    8/5/1965
  - Item 5: Vickers Incorporated, 1967; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 3)
    11/4/1967
  - Item 6: Vickers Incorporated, 1971; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 3)
    6/1/1971
  - Item 7: Viking Food Store, 1989; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 3)
    4/20/1989
  - Item 8: Vicking Corporation, 2000; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 3)
    6/22/2000
  - Item 9: Vicking Corporation, 2003; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 3)
    4/21/2003
  - Item 10: Vulcan Chain, 2001; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 3)
    8/30/2001
- WCI Steel through Westvaco Envelope, 1963-2001 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: WCI Steel Company, 1996; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 4)
    4/17/1996
  - Item 2: WCI Steel Company, 2000; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 4)
    5/1/2000
  - Item 3: WCI Steel Company, 2001; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: WDIV-TV, 1994; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 4)
    7/5/1994
  - Item 5: WEBR, 1969; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 4)
    3/27/1969
  - Item 6: Wacker Silicones Corporation, 1995; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 4)
    1/4/1995
  - Item 7: Wagner Industies, 1963; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 4)
    6/4/1963
  - Item 8: Walding Kunnan & Waiver, 1963; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 4)
    2/14/1963
  - Item 9: Wagner Press, 1982; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 4)
    5/10/1982
  - Item 10: Board of Education Warner Censol Schools, 1967; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Board of Education Warner Censol Schools, 1968; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 4)
    5/25/1968
  - Item 12: Pobate CT of County of Wayne, Michigan, 1998; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 4)
    12/1/1998
  - Item 13: Wayne County Community Colleges, 1999; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 4)
    7/30/1999
  - Item 14: Wayne State Univesity, 1996; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 4)
    6/3/1996
  - Item 15: Wayne State Univesity, 1997; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 4)
    5/3/1997
  - Item 16: Wean United, 1980; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 4)
    1/9/1980
  - Item 17: Wells Aluminum Corporation, 1994; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 4)
    7/25/1994
  - Item 18: Westing Rouse Electric, 1968; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 4)
    6/20/1968
  - Item 19: West Vaco. Envelope Division, 1991; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 4)
    1/7/1991
- Whitman and Barnes through Yale University, 1952-2002 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Women's City Club, 1966; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 5)
    12/12/1966
  - Item 1: Whilma & Baines, 1965; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 5)
    10/2/1965
  - Item 2: M.H. Wilkins Company, 1965; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 5)
    1/3/1965
  - Item 2: Woodbridge Corporation, 1995; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 5)
    3/31/1995
  - Item 3: M.H. Wilkins Company, 1959; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 5)
    10/25/1959
  - Item 3: Wrigley Stores- Allied Supermarkets, 1964; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 5)
    5/3/1964
  - Item 4: Willens-Michels Corporation, 1979; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 5)
    10/22/1979
  - Item 4: Wyandotle Chemical Corporation, 1956; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 5)
    12/6/1956
  - Item 5: Wyandotle Chemical Corporation, 1962; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 5)
    7/31/1962
  - Item 5: Wilson Foods Corporation, 1982; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 5)
    6/23/1982
  - Item 6: Wyandotle Chemical Corporation, 1964; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 5)
    12/2/1964
  - Item 6: Wilson Foods Corporation, 1982; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 5)
    7/11/1982
  - Item 7: Wilson Foods Corporation, 1982; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 5)
    8/16/1982
  - Item 7: Wyandotle Chemical Corporation, 1965; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 5)
    1/22/1965
  - Item 8: Wilson Marine Transit Company, 1969; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 5)
    2/3/1969
  - Item 8: Wyandotle General Hospital, 1986; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 5)
    12/8/1986
  - Item 9: Wise Alloys, 2002; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 5)
    1/22/2002
  - Item 9: Xact Textron, 2000; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 5)
    11/3/2000
  - Item 10: XPEDX, 2001; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 5)
    8/16/2001
  - Item 11: Yale University, 1991; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 5)
    3/11/1991
  - Item 12: Yale University, 1991; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 5)
- AT and T through ATI Allegheny Ludlum, 2003-2009 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Allegdery Sudlen Corporation, 2003; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 6)
    10/30/2003
  - Item 2: Allegdery Sudlen Corporation, 2007; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 6)
    3/6/2007
  - Item 3: Alpena Regional Medical, 2007; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 6)
    4/3/2007
  - Item 4: Arven Mentor, 2004; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 6)
    7/8/2004
  - Item 5: Arven Mentor, 2004; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 6)
    8/17/2004
  - Item 6: Avery Bakeries, 2004; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 6)
    10/29/2004
- Bay City Michigan through Buckeye Florida, 2002-2011 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: City of Bay City, Michigan (fire), 2003; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 7)
    11/5/2003
  - Item 2: Bay Fires Clearwater, Florida, 2009; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 7)
    4/1/2009
  - Item 3: Big Ridge Incorporated, 2009; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 7)
    12/16/2009
  - Item 4: Blue Cross v. Blue Shield of Michigan, 2004; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 7)
    2/25/2004